I was on the radio once.
I called into Fever 104 FM New Delhi...
...and was the fourth person
to say the phrase that pays:
"Fever 104:"
[SPEAKS IN HINDI]
That means "Fever 104:
Home of the really good current music."
It's much catchier in Hindi.
(Sheldon:)All right, these are the talking points
for my NPR interview tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)I need to make
sure they're simple enough...
(Sheldon:)...for the less educated in the audience
to understand.
(Sheldon:)Howard, look this over
and tell me what's unclear to you.
I have a Master's in engineering from the
Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
(Howard:)It required the completion of 144 units
of grad work and an original thesis.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Look this over
and tell me what's unclear to you.
(Leonard:)You know, when Sheldon gives you
homework, you don't have to do it.
(Raj:)In fact, it's better if you don't.
Otherwise, the rest of us look bad.